{
    "subject": "resource/Mighty_Mouse:_The_New_Adventures",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributor",
    "object": "resource/CBS_Television_Distribution",
    "human_readable": "Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures was distributed by CBS Television Distribution.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8975316286087036,
            "question": "Who distributed 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7542374134063721,
            "question": "What was the name of the show distributed by CBS Television Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7426502108573914,
            "question": "Is 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures' a recent television program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6188828349113464,
            "question": "Has CBS Television Distribution been involved with other animated shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5693612694740295,
            "question": "Can you name other shows distributed by CBS Television Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.562781572341919,
            "question": "What type of media company is CBS Television Distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4343954026699066,
            "question": "What was the time period when 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures' aired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4321579337120056,
            "question": "Who are some of the creators or actors involved in 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42485877871513367,
            "question": "Where would someone be able to watch 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34517616033554077,
            "question": "What genre is 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures was distributed by CBS Television Distribution.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5390_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would someone be able to watch 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5390_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the creators or actors involved in 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5390_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the time period when 'Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures' aired?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5390_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5390_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the distribution of \"Mighty Mouse: The New Adventures,\" stating that it aired on CBS and had a distributor listed as CBS Television Distribution. Therefore, the statement is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}